question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The movie The Nightmare before Christmas was all done with physical objects.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies "
                    "Interstellar and The Martian.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original script of The Matrix, the machines used humans as additional "
                    "computing power instead of batteries.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Shaquille ONeal appeared in the 1997 film Space Jam.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars"
                    " during and after filming.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically "
                    "portrayed Darth Vader.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Foodfight earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]